# Victoria Davis

Jacksonville, FL 32205 victoriadavis237\_ehe@indeedemail.com (904) 599-5440

An energetic, self-motivated, highly organized professional with over 23 years of relevant experience in office administration, account clerking, bookkeeping, and purchasing. A fast learner, dedicated to quality work with great attention to detail and the ability to multitask. An avid volunteer with a lifelong dedication to service.

## Work Experience

### **Purchasing Agent**

ComPac Filtration, Inc - Jacksonville, FL January 2019 to Present

Receive, process, and track incoming orders for service departments: electrical, plumbing, fiberglass, welding, service, front office, as well as for any other special projects and/or items needed for production. Duties include processing orders, purchase order creation and follow through, order timing and tracking, order receiving, bill and invoice processing, etc.

• Responsible for expense control, shopping vendors, various bookkeeping functions, and QuickBooks support.

## **Operations Manager/Purchasing**

DOME Headwear Co - Jacksonville, FL January 2018 to January 2019

Responsible for all office administration and management duties; expense control, supply ordering and inventory, cash processing and accountability, customer service, and various bookkeeping functions.

• Receive and process incoming orders for custom headwear, apparel and promotional items. Duties include tracking, purchase order creation, invoice processing, online order fulfillment, and shipping.

#### Accounting Clerk/Bookkeeper

Edmiston & Edmiston Certified Public Accountants - Saint Augustine, FL September 2012 to May 2018

Responsible for all aspects of account management and bookkeeping for nine companies in the tourism and commercial real estate industries. Key functions include administering accounts receivable, accounts payable, bank and account reconciliations, cash receipt and ticket/voucher reconciliations, payroll processing and reporting, sales and use tax processing and reporting, insurance maintenance, renewals and audits.

- Assist accountants with write up work, corporate tax returns, financial statements, fixed assets and accountings.
- Assist in audit scenarios, including Florida Department of Revenue and St Johns County Tax Collector.

• Created a financial reporting system, using Excel, for a local museum and gift shop struggling to track and report daily activity and cash flow.

## **Bookkeeper/Study Coordinator, FDA Trial**

U.S. Bariatric - Saint Augustine, FL October 2011 to April 2013

Responsible for bank account maintenance, account reconciliations, accounts payable, payroll processing through PEO and acted as liaison between the business office and accounting staff and CPA.

Responsible for coordinating patient visits and auditing all clinical documentation and forms within the parameters of the FDA study protocol.

### **Operations Manager/Bookkeeper**

Destiny Jewelers - Hialeah, FL March 2005 to September 2012

Responsible for all office administration and management duties; expense control, supply ordering and inventory, cash processing and accountability, customer service, employee scheduling and management, various bookkeeping functions; bank account maintenance, account reconciliations, accounts payable, payroll processing and all communications with the accountant.

### **Bookkeeper/Office Manager/Administrative Assistant**

La Estrella De Oro Joyeria - Hialeah, FL May 2004 to May 2011

## **Operations Manager/Bookkeeper**

Razz Jewelry - Fort Lauderdale, FL March 2008 to December 2010

33312

### Education

#### **Associate**

St Johns River State College Adult Education Reading Annex at ARC of Putnam County 2011 to 2017

#### **Associate of Arts**

Broward College - Fort Lauderdale, FL 2011

#### Skills

• Computer Proficiencies

Windows

- Adobe
- Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Outlook, Publisher)

- Sage (Peachtree)
- QuickBooks
- Purchasing
- Account Reconciliation
- Accounts Payable
- Tax Experience
- Order Fulfillment
- Payroll
- Accounts Receivable
- General Ledger Accounting
- Journal Entries
- Office Management
- Financial Statement Preparation
- Bank Reconciliation
- Pricing